A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Scrapbooks, 1910-1971., Extent: 1.75 cubic feet (5 boxes). (Box 169-173)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia Special Libraries (Photocopied), 1931-1955.
    - Virginia Special Libraries, 1931-1955. (Box 172, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia Library Association (Photocopied), 1910; 1933-1955.
    - Virginia Library Association, 1910; 1933-1955. (Box 172, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia War Work (Photocopied), 1942-1943.
    - Virginia War Work, 1942-1943. (Box 172, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Amherst County and Lee County (Photocopied), 1971.
    - Amherst County and Lee County, 1971. (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Dickenson County and Tazewell County (Photocopied), 1961-1964.
    - Dickenson County and Tazewell County, 1961-1964. (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Eastern Shore (Photocopied), 1956-1958.
    - Eastern Shore, 1956-1958. (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Prince William County (Photocopied), 1952-1955.
    - Prince William County (v. 1), 1952-1955. (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Prince William County (v. 2), 1952-1955. (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Washington County (Photocopied), 1954-1956.
    - Washington County (v. 1), 1954-1956. (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Washington County (v. 2), 1954-1956. (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook: Demonstration Libraries - Wise County (Photocopied), 1958-1960.
    - Wise County, 1958-1960. (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook: Works Progress Administration (WPA) (Photocopied), 1938-1942.
    - WPA (v. 1), 1938-1942. (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - WPA (v. 2), 1938-1942. (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - WPA - Virginia Library Manual, 1930. (Box 173, Folder 11)